So it's a manual?
Manuals feel great, but they suck in traffic.
You're burning up the car already.
Do you have to keep your foot on the clutch?
Well, it depends on the person.
In my case, it's too much of a hassle to put the clutch back on for a while.
So I put the clutch in half-clutch position and move slowly.
When I stop, I let off the clutch a little and step on the brake.
Like this.
What a pain in the ass!
Automatic transmission is good
Automatic transmission is so much easier.
We're already talking about the lack of time. It's already started.
Has it started?
Has it started? It's started?
I see.
You'll just have to pull yourself together, sir.
Yes, sir.
Okay, then.
Shall we go?
Yes, sir.
So, here we go again today, with our debut.
Master! I look forward to working with you.
So, it's summer now, isn't it?
It's the middle of summer, but it's the middle of summer, it's the middle of summer
a It's so hot, isn't it?
No, seriously, seriously, there are times when I feel a little bit in danger.
I've had a couple of heat stroke-like episodes where I felt like I had a stomach ache.
By the way, I do a lot of reckless things. I'm old enough to go to bars and do things like this when there's a lot of sunlight.
I've been on location alone, sweating profusely and feeling like "oh no, oh no, oh no, oh no!
I've never had that problem.
8 sturdy, that's right, that's right.
I'm very strong.
I'd like to thank my parents for that, but... well, well, well... that's why... we have a special guest.
Who's today?
Yamanaka and...Yamanaka and...
Who's he with?
Mr. Hiroshi Itsuki, it'll be great if a big star comes.
I think a big star is coming.
He's not here? Is it today? No comment? Really? That's the rumor?
What? - No, no, no. I'd like you to let me in here as soon as possible.
Who is it? Please! Uh, who is it?
Who's there? I'm so nervous.
Hello! It's Kawasaki! It's Kawasaki! You're my partner!
Excuse me, please come in.
I was passing by earlier and saw you looking bored backstage.
He had his feet on the chair the whole time.
That's right, that's right, that's right.
Well, that's why I'm here... with another guest... 66's Shingo Kawasaki.
My partner. My partner.
The two of us are always grinning and giggling, spending time together.
Even if we're not a couple, we're still together.
But they're too close, like a rumor.
I understand, I understand.
But when I see it in person, I kind of step back.
Why? Please don't pull away.
When he came on strong, he really came on strong.
Scary.
They scare me. They're dangerous.
Why do you say that?
When they're together, the atmosphere is more cheerful.
I'm glad.
I'm slipping now.
We're quite a pair, really.
I'm glad to hear you say so.
That's all I have to say.
Well, you'll be coming to the race later today, but...
I'm sure you'll come to the race later today, but I'd also like to hear your letters.
I wonder how they'll react.
What should I do?
You really know how to react.You're really good at reacting, aren't you?
You're good.
Stop it.
Okay, first of all...
I'm sorry to make this personal, but...
I founded the Kyushu Tonkotsu Ramen Study Group.
I founded a group to study Kyushu tonkotsu ramen.
I see.
I study Kyushu tonkotsu ramen every day.
By myself.
I basically do everything myself.
I do everything by myself.
It's true, we don't work together on many things, do we?
I don't usually do that at all.
Is that so?
Isn't that terrible?
It's a little late for that.
As a member of society...
Is it too late for that?
I'm not a potter or anything.
I'm not a potter.
I'm a member of the Kyushu Tonkotsu Ramen Study Group.
I have a title call.
Here, give me a good reaction.
May I?
Let's do it!
The Kyushu Tonkotsu Ramen Study Group.
Q-tan.
Cue!
Yes, that's right, isn't it?
I froze.
What's the matter?
You see...
You know...the so-called
That one, right?
Oimachi Line
Musashi Koyama
Yes, sir.
Oimachi Line?
There's a big station called Musashi Koyama
That's where the store is.
First of all, Musashikoyama station.
The area in front of the station is very beautiful.
And there's a big apartment building.
In addition, there's a big apartment building.
And there's a huge shopping street right in front of the station.
Oh, really?
Like this.
It's right in front of the station.
Wow.
About 10 seconds after you walk in, it looks like this.
What's this? And then I looked at it.
It's so long!
You know what?
Like this...
The shopping street
Wow!
It's like this, it's been going on forever
A big shopping street
Interesting way to take a picture.
Wow!
It goes on and on.
It's like a super view.
Ah.
That's what I'm talking about.That's what I'm talking about.
It's a spreader.
Oh, wow.
It's like an iPhone thing.
That's great.
Okay, so here it is.
That store.
I heard there's a great place.
That's the one...
What a surprise!
It's called Ginrei.
Wow...
Amazing atmosphere.
isn't it?
Yes, well...
It's got atmosphere.
It's faded.
Yeah, mine, too.
It's like...
It's nice.
And I
came out for the first time in the old Tokyo.
This is when it happened.
What?
I ordered ramen and waited for it.
And you know what?
When you eat ramen
I take a picture of you, don't I?
Yes, yes, yes.
With my iPhone.
And what did I do wrong?
I suddenly got a notification
I got a notification that something was going on
install
It asked me if I wanted to download it.
It was some kind of setup thing.It's something like that set-up thing.
Yes, yes, yes.
It's something that's...
Something fundamental, you know?
Download it.
Yes, yes, yes.
And do you want to download it now?
I was like, "Yeah, yeah, yeah.
And I'm like, "Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I just pressed "plastic mode".
Yes, I did.
And then...
When downloading starts on iPhone
I can't do anything.
Oh, yes, yes, yes.
I see.
Software update...
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
That's it.
I pushed it.
At that time...
Then, when the noodles came...
I still kept thinking...
Rasha...
I see.
That's why, unfortunately...
We didn't have any Rasha.
Oh...
It's a buy ball.
When it was a buy-back.
Yeah, when it was a buy-back.
I finally finished downloading it.
I was like, "How much is it worth?
I was like...
Uh...Ew.
I didn't know that.
It's so unique.
The noodles...
It's a little...
It's like...
Like yakisoba noodles.
I see.
They look a little sticky.
I see...
What's this?
I think it's a big pork from Kyushu.
Yes, yes, yes.
That's more like it.
It's so common.
Well, I'll buy one.
Delicious!
Dab some red salt on it.
Yes, sir.
It was delicious.
That's all I can say.
After all...
Thank you for the food
He drank all of it!
Wow!
Souch...
No, you didn't drink it.
The noodles sucked it up.
Really?
When you eat the noodles...
I don't know why the water came out.
Yes.
That's why.
I don't know...
If you eat it like thatThat's how I ate it.
I don't know why the water was gone.
Is that true?
Yes, I'm sure.
It's the same as if it was inside the entity.
That's right.
That's what they mean.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
Certainly.
I'm sure.
Me, too.
I was just wondering what your excuse was.
I don't know.
It's in there.
It's the same as eating it.
It's the same thing.
Yes, it's the same thing.
What's the excuse?
That's no excuse!
Yes, it is.
Well, it's like this.
The restaurant itself tastes great.
The guy was really nice.
Oh...
It's like...
This place is like this, too.
You know...
Good old-fashioned.
I hope the ramen shop will continue
I hope the ramen shop continues.
That's nice.
I hope so, too.
And...
Yes.
Well...
How about this?How about this?
Recently
Yes, sir.
Nishimasu City, Shizuoka Prefecture
Thank you very much.
Master Sarpon Ebichu!
Devil's loss was long!
Oh, no.
My deepest sympathies for your loss!
Wow!
So...
I found this in a drink vending machine.
Yes, sir.
When you are sick
Yes, sir
Go get some.
Get some.
Get some
buy me some
go buy some
go buy
Yes, sir.
I got sick.
Yes
Cold noodles to drink.
I know.
Yeah, I know.
I don't know.
Oh, my God, it was like this, wasn't it?
This is the kind of cold noodle you drink.
Yeah.Oh, wow.
It's probably cold noodle soup, like this.
Wow.
They have something like this?
The drink type?
Interesting.
This is delicious.
Oh, it's good?
Yes, it is.
Yes.
It's like drinking it cold.
It comes out cold.
Yes.
Just like that.
Drink it.
Oh!
Ah.
In a home where you can...
Often in a doable home.
I see.
Yes, it is.
And recently...
Well, Roa...
That cold noodle soup is one thing, but...
Yes.
It's very aggressive.
Oh!
And the other day...
One thing...
Yes...
This...
Huh?
What's this?
This is delicious!
It's called "chige soup".It's called chige soup.
Yeah, seriously.
That's the one.
You know what?
I bought it and drank it.
And then I drank it.
Well, my first impression was that I didn't get it at all.
Yes, yes, yes.
Like, "What the hell is this?
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
I'm mad, I'm mad, I'm mad, I'm mad, I'm mad.
Oh my God, he gets angry easily.
I'm so mad! I'm so mad!
I'm so angry.
But then I realized something.
I wrote it down well.
I didn't know what chige really tasted like.
That way...
That way.
I didn't know.
I didn't know the original recipe.
You're on the master's side.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
I'm sorry I got mad.
I wrote down what chige tastes like.
I've never had it!
What kind of chige?
What kind?
Well, it's something like that, isn't it?
It has tofu in it or something.
Korean
Soup
Soupsoup
Spicy.
Ah!
It's delicious.
No, I guess it already is.
If you knew that.
Oh, I can't believe you chewed it and drank it.
I would have thought...
I probably didn't know anything about it at the time.
This kind of thing is popular now.
It's a fad, it's a fad, it's a fad, there are a lot of them.
I see.
There's curry, too, isn't there?
Yes, there are.
Really?
And ramen soup?
Yes, we do.
Isn't that bad?
If I drank it, I'd be just like that.
I've been told not to drink it.
Drink that much.
And oden soup stock.
I know, I know!
Yes...
Yes, there is.
I love that. It's delicious.
Surprisingly... so...
Speaking of origin, corn soup is common now, right?
Yes, there is.
Yes, but...
We didn't have it when we were little.
When it first came out...
"Oh my God, you chew corn soup?
It was disgusting.
It was the same with tea.That's what you did with the tea.
You know, chewing tea.
I see.
Tea is like...
It's supposed to be drunk like that.
But now it's taken for granted.
Maybe it'll take root.
Interesting.
Oshiruko (sweet red-bean soup) is also like that, isn't it?
Oshiruko (sweet red-bean soup)
Dynamo
I like oshiruko.
It's cute.
No wonder it's cute.
The one that came in at number 8.
What a surprise.
There's one that's really good.
I was like, "Oh, my God, he's so cute!
You scared the shit out of me!
Wait a minute.
I'm really, really, really...
Next time I'm going to drink ice cream.
Next time I want to ask you about one of my favorite things.
It comes out every winter.
It's always this one...
Sweet and spicy vinegar
That's it...
Oshiruko (sweet and spicy sweet red-bean soup)
That's...
That...
Master...
I love it.
It's funny.
And...And...
And also...
By the way, in terms of the surface connection...
I wonder...
Various
The same with names.
There are masks, aren't there?
I've always wondered about this one.
I got it the other day when I was on location.
This one.
This one...
It's called "byang byang noodle".
Have you ever seen it like this?
Amazing!
You'd never find it on your first visit.
Amazing, isn't it?
It's like eating really flat noodles with a little bit of spicy food.
Biang Biang Noodles
What's this?
I did a little research and found that it's made up of one byan character.
57 strokes. Two byang byangs make 114 strokes.
And noodles have 130 strokes.
That's a lot of strokes. I'm exhausted.
I'd hate it if it was my name.
Test start! One more! But it was delicious!
But it's really good. It's really something.
Is it spicy? More spicy than Kishibeon?
I don't care about the taste at all.
I'm more interested in the characters.
It's like Oda Nobunaga, but with Nobunaga elements.
Lilissa, wow, wow!
So, if it's just a regular Kishimen, it's more like a Kishimen, like this inside.
When you boil it, it's just like this.
Like a tasuki.
You can write your wishes on it, like strips of paper.You can write your wish on it like a strip of paper.
Or you can write your wish on a strip of paper and make two wishes, like "biang biang noodles.
It's a bit like that, isn't it? - Yeah. - Was it fun? It was fun.
I'm getting dumped all of a sudden. It's like this... all the time.
We'll make an assignment.
And... well...
There's a birthday girl here. Let's raise our hands.
No, I'm in May... a little bit.
What's that?
I don't get it.
Wasn't it July, Shinko?
I was born on July 3rd.
That's close enough.
June, Master? Twenty-seven.
I'm close, 27.
I should have raised my hand.
Of course you should have.
January, right? January for me.
I'm in May.
Aren't you in the summer group?
Summer group.
I like it.
Not May?
I don't want to be in the summer group. I don't want to be in the summer group.
I don't get it.
I don't think they call it summer in the beginning of May.
They say it's almost the second half of May.
That's why I celebrated my birthday...
That's all!
Thank you very much for coming!
As usual, we have a present for you!
Yay!
I don't know... last year, I got a lot of tomato goods.
You really love tomatoes, don't you?
Even your catchphrase says you're a lycopene girl who loves tomatoes.
I see.I see.
That's why your skin is white.
It's written something like French.
Esladune.
Wow, I get it.
Esladun.
So you're an ST Lo?
Is it because I like beauty?
No, or maybe it's just the bag.
Because it's gold there.
It's golden there.
Daily Charge from Tamamin
Happy Birthday, Master!
Thank you very much.
I'd like to know a little bit about what it's about.
Okay, open.
Face pack.
I love beauty.
She wants me to use this to cleanse my skin.
It's beautiful enough, isn't it?
What if it's even prettier?
It's too smooth.
On top of this.
Can you spin me around?
I'm sorry.
That was bad.
That felt really bad.
Well, well, well.
Did you fight?
He hit me and hit me and hit me.
I see.
So this is the Korean way.
It's Korean.
Isn't it cold?
Maybe.
Oh, my God.Oh, my God.
I put this on my face.
You put it on your face and it pulls it off.
You should try it.
I should?
I'll teach you how to wash your face first.
I can't just wash my face like a normal person.
No, you can't.
I'd like to know.
Well, well, well.
There's this.
What's this?
What is it?
A fan?
What?
It's summer
Oh, wow.
And this is a beauty brand fan.
That's amazing.
SR?
It's so classy!
And what's this?
It's amazing.
I don't know.
Like a prize.
Like money.
Don't say that.
I don't know.
It's a pack.
I'm so happy!
It's a beauty product.
It's a really good one.A very nice one.
High-end.
Thank you.
Yay!
That looks amazing and so good!
The master is a face pack.
He's very particular about what he does.
I know.
He's a certified cosmetologist.
She has.
S-Te?
She's a beauty specialist.
No, no, no.
Yes!
Thank you very much.
By the way, we were just talking about this.
But since we're here, let's hear it.
Face wash.
I'd like to try Iroha's medicine.
For men...
Really...
I'm just going to start with the basics.
Just starting with the basics.
I think you can get a lot of sugar on your skin.
First of all
Lukewarm water
Lukewarm water.
It's a pain in the ass.
It's a pain in the ass, so just touch it with your hand.
If it feels warm to the touch, it's fine.
Lukewarm?
After lukewarm water.
After you take a lukewarm bath, you should take a cold one.
It tightens the pores.
Like blackheads on your nose.
the size of the blackheads on your noseIt's getting smaller and smaller.
That's where the men start.
You can start with
Use lukewarm water.
Wash your face properly.
That's normal.
It's like a belly wash.
That's not quite the right word.
You're supposed to "belch.
Splash, splash, splash.
Is that okay?
I don't think he's done anything wrong.
That's enough.
I haven't done anything either.
I've never dripped anything.
I've never put a drop of anything on my face.
I've had a make-up artist do it.
It's like a compilation.
But this...
You said you'd take it off.
Take off the makeup.
Do that first.
Next step
If you feel like washing your face
You can use anything you want.
Anything cheap, like 100 yen or whatever is cheap.
Just use a lathering net to make a face wash.
Make sure you get a good lather.
A lathering net is good.
It'll change your skin a lot.
You mean like a lathering net?
Yes.
So foaming is better?
It gets into the pores.
It gets into the pores and washes them.
If you rub with your hands...When you rub it with your hands.
There's simply no damage to the skin.
That's how it works.
With a gentle elastic lather.
By washing thoroughly
You can get the most out of your face wash.
That's great.
I know the program has changed.
It's a commentary, too.
The master can't stop talking about beauty.
Maybe you should do it on BS or something.
You could get him to do it for an hour or so.
He always starts talking on his delivery or something.
For an hour straight.
That's great.
I'm sure you'll learn a lot.
If you need anything else, just ask.
You're right, it was a bit of a shock right off the bat.
Lukewarm water.
I've never done that before.
I've never tried boiling water. It dries out the skin.
Boiling water?
That sounds like something you'd do.
Hot water.
Men often take showers in the winter when it's cold.
So they take a shower in the winter.
It's like a desert.
Desert?
I was a desert?
Like the Tokyo desert.
Like you're a desert.
You should never apply it.
If you're going to take care of your skin...
Lukewarm water even in winter.
Even if you take a shower...
Basically, take a lukewarm shower.Make it as warm as possible.
And when you use it for a bath
Use lukewarm water for as long as possible
That's what I mean.
If you apply a stimulus to the skin
You'll be surprised.
Maybe this is like a sauna or something.
But that's just...
It's like a heat shock.
Then you take a bath in the water.
And then you go to the water bath, and you get a little squeak.
But that's okay?
Sudden shocks are fine.
I see.
No, no, no, no, no.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
I'll let the live feed do the talking.
Devil Charge.
Devil Charge!
Happy Birthday, Mr. Devil Charge
Mr. Kozhikode.
Happy Birthday
Happy birthday to you
It's true...
Your skin is so smooth!
No, really.
You're right.
If I told you that, you wouldn't trust me.
It's lukewarm.
That's for sure.
You don't like it?
It's amazing.
It's so white.
Here's the two of us in a row.
Me too.
I want to see this shot of them together.This video shot of the two of them.
It's hard to believe it's the same human being, isn't it?
It's just...
It's amazing.
Well, well, well.
You're the live one.
Next week.
Usually at 8:00 p.m.
So, I'll see you all again.
I hope to see you all soon.
Thank you very much for your time today.
Thank you very much.
See you again.
And again.
See you soon.
See you later.
Bye-bye.